

## **SKILLS**

### **JavaScript**

Node Js Express Js React Js Vue Js React Native

#### PHP

Native Laravel

#### **Database**

MySQL Redis Firebase



# CONTACT

- A Bandar Lampung
- **L** +62 822 8159 7835
- 🔽 rindangramadhan10@gmail.com
- in Rindang Ramadhan
- f Rindang Ramadhan
- RIndangRamadhan

# RINDANG RAMADHAN

PROGRAMMER

### **PROFILE**

I am a Full Stack Web Developer since 2016 with strong passion to learn new things.

I am familiar with a few Javascript frameworks & PHP frameworks, and I have developed Web for a production system with Vue Js & React Js as frontend and Laravel & Express Js as Backend. Currently I am interested and learning about React Native.

### **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2019 **Glovory** 

> Full Stack Developer, Bandar Lampung I create and manage Web Application with Express JS as Backend & Vue JS as Frontend. And I contributed to one of the Android projects using

React Native.

2018 - 2019 **Kosasih Group (Lampung)** 

> Software Engineer, Bandar Lampung I design, create and manage Web Application with Express JS as Backend & React JS as Frontend. And I made an Android-based timesheet application with React Native for employee attendance activities in the company. I also analyze problems and provide technical solutions

to application problems.

2016 - 2018 PT. Andaglos Global Teknologi

Web Developer, Bandar Lampung

I design, create and manage Web Application with PHP Native or Framework (Laravel as Backend & VueJs as Frontend). I alse analyze problems and provide technical solutions to application

problems.

# **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2015

2018 - 2018 **Learn React Native** 

Andaglos Academy, Bandar Lampung Basic and Fundamental of Javascript &

Introduction to React Native

2016 - 2017 **Full Stack Web Developer** 

Pesantren Programmer Ibnu Kosasih, Bandar

Lampung

**Teknik Komputer & Jaringan** 

SMK KH. GHALIB, Pringsewu - Lampung

Formal education